Friends, welcome again to our
[music]
youtube2 type and search it
friends, as soon as you search it, its
official website
will open after the official website opens
friends, you will see the option of raise a complaint here in the
name of icicibank.com friends, you have to click here
because this website
is the website of ICICI Bank from where the complaint is raised,
whatever problem or difficulty you are facing,
you can complain to IIC Bank from here,
I will definitely solve your problem,
so friends, now you have to
click on the option of raise complaint of ICICI Bank, here you will
get the option of send an email on the top side,
so here you have to click on send an email,
after clicking here friends,
you have to select product service at the top,
here you have to select product service,
whatever problem you are facing, what
problem you are facing, you will
select the problem there and select the region here, so
friends, like you are facing
problem in savings account, mobile
banking  If you are facing any problem in my internet banking, my
insurance, deposit team, current account,
credit card or any of these options, then
you have to
select the option, friends, I am facing
problem in savings account here, so
I will click here,
after clicking here, friends,
you will see the second option, select
query related to here, friends, you have to
click here, now you have to
put whichever option you want on this, according to you,
what problem are you facing in your savings
account, friends, here I am facing
transaction related problem,
statement related, pension related, mobile banking
related, EMI related, debit card
related, whatever problem you are facing,
friends, you have to select this, I am facing
transaction related problem here,
after this friends, you have to select the third option again,
which problem are you facing in query,
friends, I am facing
problem in UPI transaction related here, then I will
click here,
after this friends, you have to go down to
additional details, here you have to
enter your full name, whatever is your name,
inside the account  After entering the number, friends,
you have to fill your account number or
application number here,
friends, after entering the account number, you have to
enter the query here at the bottom,
you have to enter the details here,
friends, what problem are you facing,
you have to fill it in the details here,
whatever problem you are facing, it
is written here remaining character 1000 words,
you can write up to 1000 words also, friends
here,
after this, friends, you have to fill the email ID,
whatever is your email ID,
after filling the email ID, friends,
you have to fill the mobile number at the bottom,
after filling your mobile number, friends,
you have to enter the area code here, which is the
code of your area,
after filling the area code, friends,
you have to fill the phone number at the bottom, whatever is
your phone number which you had put above,
you have to enter the phone number here, friends,
here friends, how are these eight numbers looking,
what is the problem,
friends, first you have to select this here, which
mobile number are you, here
you have to select India,
friends, after selecting India,
friends, you have to enter the telephone number at the bottom  But you have to
select India
[Music]
India here friends
after selecting India you have to
enter the code here friends you have to enter the phone number
whatever your phone number
is friends keep in mind you have to enter the same mobile
number here which is linked in your bank account on
which you
want to SMS whatever your query will be the
bank people will solve it then the
solution of your query will be sent to your email or mobile
number through SMS so you have to
enter the same mobile number here which is
linked to your bank or the
mobile number which is active in your account number or
you can enter your active mobile number friends
after this friends you have to fill the captcha on this
captcha friends you have to fill the same
after filling the captcha friends you have to enter I
authorize IIC Bank and RIP with to
call me with reference to my query
request so friends keep in mind you have to
enter the mobile number which is active you
mean active do not enter such a number which
is not activated otherwise the bank people will
not be able to call you they will
not be able to send you any message on SMS or email
after this friends you have to click on submit
like friends you
click on submit  If you do this, your complaint will be
raised in ICICI Bank and this complaint will be accepted by them.
Now the people of ICICI Bank
solve your complaint within one to seven days,
if they do not do this, then it takes
maximum 15 days.
Friends, they will solve your complaint, it is
possible that they will do it very soon, it will not take even a day. The
facility and online facility of ICICI Bank is
very good, their payment is also
very fast, whatever you do, so
friends, I hope you liked this video.
If you liked this video, then
you can like, share and subscribe to our channel
and press the bell icon
so that in future you keep getting such
helpful videos from our channel. So,
thank you friends, see you
in the next video with the next content.